const contest_2_2 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the magnitude of the magnetic force on a straight $0.5 \\mathrm{~m}$ long wire carrying a current of $2 \\mathrm{~A}$ in a uniform $20 \\mathrm{~T}$ magnetic field that makes an angle of $30^{\\circ}$ with the wire.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$10 N$\n$$\nF=B I l \\sin \\theta=20 T \\times 2 A \\times 0.5 m \\times \\sin 30^{\\circ}=10 N\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Magnetic Force", "Physics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the rms speed of $5.4 \\times 10^{23}$ ideal gas molecules each of mass $4.6 \\times 10^{-26} \\mathrm{~kg}$ contained in a vessel of volume $2.6 \\times 10^{-3} \\mathrm{~m}^{3}$ when the pressure of the gas is $72 \\mathrm{kPa}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$150 \\mathrm{~ms}^{-1}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["RMS Speed", "Ideal Gas Law"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A $3.0 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object moving at $8.0 \\mathrm{~m} \\mathrm{~s}^{-1}$ strikes a rigid wall directly and bounces off at $8.0 \\mathrm{~m} \\mathrm{~s}^{-1}$. Find the impulse of the force that acts on the object in its collision with the wall.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$48 \\mathrm{~kg} \\mathrm{~m} \\mathrm{~s}^{-1}$ perpendicular to and away from the wall\n$$\n\\Delta p=2 m u \\hat{n}=2 \\times 3.0 \\mathrm{~kg} \\times 8.0 \\mathrm{~ms}^{-1} \\hat{n}=48 \\mathrm{~kg} \\mathrm{~ms}^{-1} \\hat{n}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Impulse", "Momentum"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A buffer is made up of a weak acid and its conjugate base. Give the expression for the $\\mathrm{pH}$ in terms of the pKa of the acid and the concentrations of the acid and the conjugate base in solution.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\mathrm{pH}=\\mathrm{pKa}+\\log _{10} \\frac{[\\text { Base }]}{[\\text { Acid }]} \\quad$ Or\n$$\n\\mathrm{pH} \\quad=\\quad \\mathrm{pKa}-\\log _{10} \\frac{[\\text { Acid }]}{[\\text { Base }]}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Buffer Solution", "pH Calculation"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "State if an aqueous solution of magnesium chloride is acidic or neutral or basic.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Acidic",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Acid-Base Chemistry", "Aqueous Solutions"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "What is the general name for substances added to plastics to make them softer and flexible?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Plasticiser(s).",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Polymers", "Plasticisers"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Name the multipolar neuron which is located entirely within the central nervous system",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Interneuron",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Neurons", "Central Nervous System"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Give the location and function of thylakoids",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Inside the chloroplast, it traps solar energy",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Chloroplast", "Thylakoids"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Name the phase of the cardiac cycle in which the ventricles relax.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Diastolic phase",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Cardiac Cycle", "Diastole"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the values of $x$ for which the given function $f(x)=(x-1) /\\left(x^{2}-4\\right)(x+1)$ is not defined",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$x= \\pm 2,-1$\n[denominator $=(x-2)(x+2)(x+1)$, hence not defined for $x=2,-2,-1]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Functions", "Undefined Points"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the area of the finite region bounded by the curves\n$y=x^{2}+1$ and the line $y=10$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "36 sq. units\n$\\left[x^{2}+1=10, x^{2}=9, x= \\pm 3, A=\\int_{-3}^{3}\\left(9-x^{2}\\right) d x=\\left.\\left(9 x-x^{3} / 3\\right)\\right|_{-3} ^{3}=(27-9)-(-27+9)=36\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Area under Curve", "Integration"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "State a necessary condition for the compound statement ' $P$ and $Q^{\\text {' }}$ to be true",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Both $P$ and $Q$ must be true.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logic", "Compound Statements"]
    }
]
export default contest_2_2